A Guide to the Papers of William B. Spong, 1965-1974
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Federal Files
  - Casework Files
    - Casework Files (Alphabetical Arrangement by Organization)
      - Transportation Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - Treasury Casework Files A-Z 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 137)
      - United States Information Agency Casework Files A-Z 1968 (Box 137)
      - Veterans Administration Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968, 7 folders (Box 137)
    - Casework Files (Alphabetical Arrangement by Person's Name)
      - Casework Files Ac-Cz ca. 1969-1970, 10 folders (Box 137)
      - Casework Files Da-R ca. 1969-1970, 23 folders (Box 138)
      - Casework Files S-Z ca. 1969-1970, 8 folders (Box 139)
    - Casework Files by Organization (Chronologically Arranged)
      - Agriculture Casework Files 1970-1972 (Box 139)
      - Air Force Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Army Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Civil Service Commission Casework Files 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 139)
      - Commerce Casework Files 1970-1972 (Box 139)
      - Defense Casework Files 1970-1972 (Box 139)
      - District of Columbia Government Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Embassies Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Federal Communications Commission Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - General Accounting Office Casework Files 1970-1972 (Box 139)
      - General Services Administration Casework Files 1970-1972 (Box 139)
      - Health, Education and Welfare Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Housing and Urban Development Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Interior Casework Files 1970-1972 (Box 139)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Justice Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Justice - Immigration & Naturalization Service Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Labor Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Marine Corps Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Miscellaneous 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Navy 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 139)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Postal Service Casework Files 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 139)
      - Selective Service System Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Small Business Administration Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Social Security Casework Files 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 139)
      - State Department Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Transportation Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Transportation - Federal Aviation Administration Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Transportation - U.S. Coast Guard Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Treasury Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Treasury - Internal Revenue Service Casework Files 1971-1972 (Box 139)
      - Veterans Administration Casework Files 1970-1972 (Box 139)
- General
  - Administration 1966-1971 (Box 140)
  - Administration - General Office Procedures, including form letters 1968 (Box 140)
  - Administration - Mail [Form Letters] 1967-1968, 4 folders (Box 140)
  - Administration - Memoranda 1967-1968 (Box 140)
  - 1966 Campaign Files
    - Campaign - Address & Mailing Lists 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Advertising Materials 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Analysis of the General Election & Primary by Ralph Eisenberg 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Battle, Governor John - Primary Statement 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Byrd, Harry F. re Speeches 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Campaign Worker List 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Contribution Thank You Letters 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Correspondence 1965-1966, 8 folders (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Correspondence of Joseph E. Blackburn, State Campaign Manager 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Correspondence re Legislation (Post- Election) 1966 Dec (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Correspondence with Senator William V. Rawlings 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Democratic Committees of Northern Virginia 1966 (Box 140)
    - Campaign - Districts 1-10 1966, 3 folders (Box 140)
    - Campaign - District 10 Survey for Democratic Primary, with Notes 1966, 2 folders (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Editorials, etc. re Spong 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Etheridge, Jack 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Finance Committee 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Form Letters 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - "Identification of Voting Influences & Challenges in the November 1966 General Election" by Richard A. Page 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Industrial Plants with more than 500 Employees ca. 1965 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Agriculture 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Banks & Truth-in-Lending 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Civil Rights & Race 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Civil Rights & Race (Richmond) 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Education 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Ethics 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Federal Employees 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - James River Channel, Salem Dam & Gathright Dam 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Labor 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Medicare 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Richmond Coliseum 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Right-to-Work 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Rural Electric Cooperatives 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Savings & Loan 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Urban Renewal 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Issues - Veterans & Defense 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - "Kook" Letters 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - League of Women Voters Questionnaire 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Martin & Woltz 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Memoranda 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Memoranda from Benet Gellman 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Miscellaneous 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Newsclippings - Miscellaneous 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Newsclippings re Topics (not found under Campaign -Issues above) 2 folders 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Organization 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Photographs 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Platform of Bill Spong 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Political Districts 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Poll Workers 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - "A Post Election Survey of the 10th Congressional District of Virginia" by Louis Harris and Associates, Inc. 1962 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Radio & TV 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Republican James P. Ould, Jr. 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Requests for Information 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Senator A. Willis Robertson - Age, Absentee Record, etc. 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Sample Ballots & Campaign Literature 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Schedules 1966 (Box 141)
    - Campaign - Speaker Requests 1966, 2 folders (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Spong Primary Victory Congratulation Letters 1966 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Strategy 1966 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - "A Study of the Political Climate in Virginia" prepared by Oliver Quayle & Company, Inc. 1966 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Tribute to Harry F. Byrd, Sr. 1966 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - "Virginia Politics in Evolution" A Paper by John G. Milliken 1966 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Volunteers 1966 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Voter Registration 1966 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Voting Record of Senator A. Willis Robertson 1966 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Voting Record of Bill Spong 1966 (Box 142)
  - 1972 Campaign Files
    - Campaign - Advertising 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Committee for an Honest Campaign Working Papers 1971-1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Congressional Record Index References to Senator Spong 1967-1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Coordinators 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Correspondence 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Democratic Committees 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Editorials 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Environmental Statements & Material 1967-1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Financial Disclosures 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Mailing Lists 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Memoranda 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Miscellaneous 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Photographs 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Press Releases & Statements 1972, 4 folders (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Report on "Washington, D.C. Five Metro Counties Net Weekly Circulation Estimates" 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Schedules 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Telegrams Sent 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Voting Record of Representative William L. Scott 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Voting Record of Senator William B. Spong, Jr. 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - Voting Records and Issue Position Comparisons Between Spong & Scott 1972 (Box 142)
    - Campaign - "Where I Stand" Statement 1972 (Box 142)
    - National Politics 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 143)
    - National Politics - Committee Assignments 1971-1972 (Box 143)
    - National Politics - Democratic Convention 1968-1971 (Box 143)
    - National Politics - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee 1969-1972 (Box 143)
    - National Politics - Humphrey, Hubert H. 1968 (Box 143)
    - National Politics - McCarthy, Eugene 1968, 3 folders (Box 143)
    - National Politics - National Democratic Committee 1967-1971 (Box 143)
    - National Politics - Presidential Election 1968, 2 folders (Box 143)
    - National Politics - Presidential Transition Act 1969 (Box 143)
    - National Politics - Young Democratic Clubs of America 1967-1970 (Box 143)
    - Public Activities - Appointment Books 1967-1972, 6 bound volumes (Box 143)
    - Public Activities - Appointments 1971-1972, 6 folders (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Appointments - Portsmouth 1970-1972 (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Awards 1966-1967 (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Chairmanships & Memberships 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Chairmanships & Memberships - Honorary Responsibilities 1971 (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Chairmanships & Memberships - Pi Kappa Alpha Dinner 1971 (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Chairmanships & Memberships - Presidential Classroom 1968-1972 (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Chairmanships & Memberships - UNESCO 1967-1968 (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Congressional Record Index & Inserts re Spong 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Financial Disclosure 1967 (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Guest Registers 1967-1972, 8 bound volumes (Box 144)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted 1967-1972, 18 folders (Box 145)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Botetourt County 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Ditchley Conference 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Friends Association 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Jefferson/Jackson Dinner 1972 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Law Day at the University of Virginia 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - NATO 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Portsmouth 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Reynolds Homestead 1972 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Southwest Virginia 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Staunton Breakfast 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Tidewater 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Invitations Accepted - Waynesboro 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Speakers 1967-1970, 5 folders (Box 146)
    - Public Activities - Trip to Southwest Virginia 1971 (Box 146)
    - Public Relations 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 146)
    - Public Relations - Articles & Reports by Spong 1971-1972 (Box 146)
    - Public Relations - Congressional Reprints 1968, 1970-1972, n.d., 3 folders (Box 146)
    - Public Relations - Grant Announcements - ACTION through General Services Administration 1967-1972, 7 folders (Box 146)
    - Public Relations - Grant Announcements - Health, Education & Welfare through Office of Economic Opportunity 1967-1972, n.d., 22 folders (Box 147)
    - Public Relations - Grant Announcements - Office of Economic Opportunity through Transportation 1967-1972, n.d., 6 folders (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailing Lists 1967-1968, 1972, 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailing Lists - Additions 1968-1972, 4 folders (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailing Lists - Changes 1967, 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailing Lists - Deletions 1968, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailing Lists - Solicitation of Lists 1970, 1972, 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailing Lists - Winter, Rolland 1969-1972 (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailouts 1967 (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailouts - High School Principals 1967-1968 Jan (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailouts - Marshall Library 1967-1968 (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Mailouts - Virginia Scenic Historyland 1967 (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Media Address List n.d. (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Memoranda re Voting Record & Statements re Legislative Issues 1967-1969, n.d., 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Newsletter 1968, 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Political Ratings 1967-1972, n.d. (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Political Ratings - Americans for Constitutional Action 1967-1969 (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Political Ratings - Americans for Democratic Action 1969 (Box 148)
    - Public Relations - Political Ratings - American Security Council 1970 (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Political Ratings - Committee on Political Education [C.O.P.E.] AFL-CIO 1965-1969 (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Political Ratings - National Farmer's Union 1968-1970 (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Press 1966 Dec-1972, 3 folders (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Press Assistant's Files 1971-1972, 5 folders (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Press - Hong Kong Song Bill 1967 (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Press - Newsletter Questionnaire 1971, 2 folders (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Press - Newspapers 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Press - Newspapers - Interview with Don Hill, Virginian-Pilot Washington Writer 1970 (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Press - Radio 1967-1972, n.d., 4 folders (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Press - Television 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Questionnaires 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Richmond Law Review Article 1971 (Box 149)
    - Public Relations - Speeches 1967-1971 May, 23 folders (Box 150)
    - Public Relations - Speeches 1971 Jun-1972, 10 folders (Box 151)
    - Public Relations - Speeches - Beepers 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 151)
    - Public Relations - Speeches - Campaign 1966, 2 folders (Box 151)
    - Public Relations - Speeches - Correspondence 1967-1972 (Box 151)
    - Public Relations - Speeches - Notes 1967, n.d. (Box 151)
    - Public Relations - The Spong Report 1968-1971 (Box 151)
    - Public Relations - Texas Law Review Article 1971 (Box 152)
    - Public Relations - Voting Record 1970, 1972, n.d. (Box 152)
    - Public Relations - Voting Record - Chronologies 1967-1969 (Box 152)
    - State Affairs 1967-1972, 20 folders (Box 152)
    - State Affairs - Advice 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Agriculture 1967-1972 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Agriculture - Farm Tour 1969 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Air Pollution 1968-1972, 6 folders (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Alcohol Beverage Control Board 1967-1972 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Chamber of Commerce 1967-1971 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Alexandria through Quantico 1971-1972 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Chesapeake 1970-1971 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Newport News 1970-1972 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Norfolk 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Portsmouth 1967-1972 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Portsmouth Condemnation & Redevelopment 1968-1970 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Portsmouth - Londontown Mfg. Company 1969 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Portsmouth - USO Facility 1969-1970 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Richmond 1967-1972 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Richmond - All American City Award 1967 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Roanoke 1967-1972 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Cities - Virginia Beach 1967-1971 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Complaints 1967-1968 (Box 153)
    - State Affairs - Complaints 1969-1972 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Conservation 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Counties 1968-1972 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Counties - Accomac through Wise 1968-1970 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Counties - Fairfax 1967-1972 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Counties - Loudoun 1967-1971 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Counties - Nansemond 1970-1972 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Counties - Nelson 1971 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Conservation - Outdoor Recreation 1967-1971 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Conservation - Outdoor Recreation - Burling Tract 1970 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Conservation - Outdoor Recreation - Commission of Game & Inland Fisheries 1971 (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Conservation - Water Resources 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Disasters 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Disasters - Central Virginia Floods 1969, 1971, 4 folders (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Education 1967-1971, 5 folders (Box 154)
    - State Affairs - Education 1972, 4 folders (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Contracts 1970 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Educational Opportunity Week 1968-1969 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Elementary Education 1967-1972 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Henrico Schools 1970-1971 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Higher Institutions 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Higher Institutions - Ferrum College 1967-1972 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Higher Institutions - Frederick Military Academy 1967-1968 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Higher Institutions- Hampden- Sydney 1968-1972 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Higher Institutions - Mary Baldwin through Virginia State 1967-1972 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Higher Institutions - Medical College of Virginia 1967-1972 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Higher Institutions - University of Virginia 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Higher Institutions - Virginia Commonwealth 1971-1972 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Higher Institutions - Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1967-1972 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Reply to Superintendent 1972 (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Richmond Schools Consolidation 1972 Jan-Feb 9, 3 folders (Box 155)
    - State Affairs - Education - Richmond Schools Consolidation 1972 Feb-Nov, 3 folders (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - Education - School Newsletters 1967-1972 (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - Education - Secondary Education 1967-1972 (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - Education - Spong Courses 1972 (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - Elections 1968-1971 (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - Election of 1968 1968, 2 folders (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - Environmental Organizations 1970-1972, 6 folders (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - General Assembly 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - General Assembly - Constitutional Changes 1969-1970 (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - General Assembly - Constitutional Changes - Abortion 1970 (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - Governor's Office 1967-1972 (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - Health 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 156)
    - State Affairs - Health - Contacts 1970 (Box 157)
    - State Affairs - Health - Hospitals 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - State Affairs - Health - Mental Institutions 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 157)
    - State Affairs - Health - Southwestern Hospital & Training School 1970-1971 (Box 157)
    - State Affairs - Health - Visual Aids 1971, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - State Affairs - Highways & Roads 1967-1972 Jul, 14 folders (Box 157)
    - State Affairs - Highways & Roads 1972 Aug-Dec, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Highways & Roads - Berryville through Shirley Highway 1967-1972 (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Highways & Roads - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel 1969-1970 (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Highways & Roads - Hampton Roads 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Highways & Roads - I-66 1970-1972, 4 folders (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Highways & Roads - I-77 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Highways & Roads - Richmond Expressway 1968-1969 (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Highways & Roads - Richmond Turnpike 1972 (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Industry 1967-1972 (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Insurance 1971-1972 (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Judiciary 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Judiciary - Prisons 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Judiciary - Prisons - Louisa County 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 158)
    - State Affairs - Labor 1967-1972 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Labor - Workman's Compensation 1967-1970 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Laws and Legislation 1967-1970 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Laws and Legislation - Liquor-by-the- Drink 1968 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Division of Motor Vehicles (with bound report) 1968-1972 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - National Guard 1967-1970 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - State Corporation Commission 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - State Employment Commission 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - State Organizations 1967-1972 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - State Police 1967-1972 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - State Port Authority 1969-1972 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Taxation 1967-1972 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Tourism 1967-1972 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Tourism - Senator Eagleton 1969 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Utilities 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Utilities - Appalachian Power Company 1965-1967, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Utilities - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Company Toll Charges 1967-1969 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Utilities - Virginia Power Company 1967-1969 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Voting Rights 1971-1972 (Box 159)
    - State Affairs - Water Pollution 1968-1972, 9 folders (Box 160)
    - State Affairs - Water Pollution - Abingdon 1971 (Box 160)
    - State Affairs - Water Pollution - Fairfax 1970-1971 (Box 160)
    - State Affairs - Water Pollution - James River 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 160)
    - State Affairs - Water Pollution - Kilmernock 1971 (Box 160)
    - State Affairs - Water Pollution - Middleton 1971 (Box 160)
    - State Affairs - Water Pollution - Occoquan Creek 1968-1970 (Box 160)
    - State Affairs - Water Pollution - Potomac River 1969-1972, 4 folders (Box 160)
    - State Affairs - Water Pollution - Potomac River - Potomac Sand & Gravel 1970-1971 (Box 160)
    - State Affairs - Welfare 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 161)
    - State Politics 1967-1972, 7 folders (Box 161)
    - State Politics - Democratic Primary 1967-1971 (Box 161)
    - State Politics - Elections 1967, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 161)
    - State Politics - Elections - District 1 - District 10 ca 1968-1971, 9 folders (Box 161)